真是令人难以置信,已过了半个小时
Unbelievable! It's been half an hour.
如果这是卡通 你应该看起来像火腿一样
If this was a cartoon,you'd look like a ham now.
-女侍在那儿,嗨,小姐…等等 -是菲比!
-There's the waitress. Hello,miss! -It's Phoebe!
-好的,这些就是全部啦? -等等,你来这儿干什么?
-Okay,will that be all? -Wait. What are you doing here?
我本来在那儿,然后你叫 “嗨,小姐.”所以我就过来了
I was over there. Then you said,"Hello,miss." So I'm here.
不,你怎么会在这儿工作?
No,how come you're working here?
因为这儿离我的住处很近 而且围裙也很漂亮
Because it's close to where I live,and the aprons are cute.
-可以重来吗? -好的,我到那边去
-Can we start over? -Okay,I'm gonna be over here.
六人行 第1季 第16集 第17集 双胞胎
The One With Two Partsl
我不知道它是不是在考验我
I don't know whether he's testing me...
我的猴子已失去控制
... but my monkey is out of control!
它不断清除我答录机上的留言
He keeps erasing the messages on my machine.
应该是个意外
Supposedly by accident.
哦,是的,我做过这种事
Oh,yeah,I've done that.
它连续三天在我看报纸前
And then he got to the newspaper before I did...
在猜字游戏上尿尿
...and peed all over the crossword!
这我没做过
I've never done that.
昨晚,我不知道他做了什么 他到处蹦来蹦去!
Last night,I don't know what he did but there were capers everywhere!
-她看起来和她姐姐完全一样 -我看到不同之处
-She looks exactly like her sister. -I'm saying I see a difference.
她们是双胞胎
They're twins.
我不管,菲比是菲比,乌苏拉很火辣
I don't care. Phoebe's Phoebe. Ursula's hot!
你知道我们怎么说这种事情?
You know how we talk about things?
-别再谈论那事了 -好吧
-Let's not do that anymore. -All right.
-菲比,猜我们今天遇见谁? -哦,好玩!好的
-Pheebs,guess who we saw today? -Oh,fun! Okay.
-连恩尼逊（电影演员） -不是
-Liam Neeson. -No.
-莫利塞弗（记者） -不是
-Morley Safer. -No.
-剪我头发的女人! -这会是一个很长的游戏
-The lady who cuts my hair! -This could be a very long game.
-你姐姐,乌苏拉 -哦,真的?
-Your sister,Ursula. -Oh,really?
-她在那儿工作… -瑞菲餐厅,我知道
-She works at that place.... -Riff's. I know.
你知道?因为她说你们已多年不说话
You do? She said you guys haven't talked in years.
对,她胖吗?
So,is she fat?
从我的角度看不会
Not from where I was standing.
你从什么角度?
Where were you standing?
菲比,你们合不来?
Pheebs,so you guys just don't get along?
这只是姐妹之间的事
It's mostly just dumb sister stuff.
大家都认为她漂亮
Everyone always thought of her as the pretty one.
她先学会走路 虽然我是在当天稍后学会的
She was the first to walk even though I did it later that same day.
对我爸妈而言那就已经不新鲜了
But to my parents,by then it was,"Yeah,what else is new?"
菲比,抱歉,我得走了 我得去学习无痛分娩法
I'm sorry. I've gotta go. I've got Lamaze class.
我得去参加地球科学班 健身房见了
And I've got earth science,but I'll catch you in gym?
-就你和卡萝两人去? -不,苏珊也要去
-ls this just gonna be you and Carol? -Susan will be there too.
那有爸爸,女同志…全部的父母都会到
We've got dads,we've got lesbians. The whole parenting team.
-这样不是会很奇怪? -不会的,一开始或许会
-lsn't that gonna be weird? -lt might have been at first...
现在我已坦然面对
... but now I'm comfortable with it.
-罗斯,那是我的外套 -我知道
-Ross,that's my jacket. -I know.
我们姓罗斯特,我是洁西他叫麦可
Hi. We're the Rostens. I'm J. C. and he's Michael.
我们有一个男孩和一个女孩
And we're having a boy and a girl.
厉害,下一位
Good for you. All right,next?
我叫罗斯,我儿子在那儿
I'm Ross Geller. And that's my boy in there.
她叫卡萝,这位是苏珊
And this is Carol Willick. And this is Susan Bunch.
苏珊是卡萝的…
Susan is Carol's....
下一位是谁?
Who's next?
抱歉,苏珊是…
Sorry,Susan is...?
-苏珊是卡萝的朋友 -生活拍档
-Carol's friend. -Life partner.
就像伙伴
Like buddies.
-好像恋人 -你知道女人能有多亲近的
-Like lovers. -You know how close women can get.
-我们俩住在一起 -我俩曾经结过婚
-We live together. -I was married to her.
-卡萝,不是我 -有点复杂了
-Carol,not me. -It's a bit complicated.
-但是我们不错 -绝对的!
-But we're fine. -Absolutely!
双胞胎,好像要生两次
So,twins! That's like two births.
噢!
Ouch!
彼此,海伦
to you too,Helen.
-妮娜.布克宾德来找你 -好的,让她进来
-Nina Bookbinder is here to see you. -Okay,send her in.
-妮娜,快进来 -你想见我?
-Come on in. -You wanted to see me?
我刚看过你的资料 你一直填迟你周五数字的日期
I was reviewing your data. You've been postdating your Friday numbers.
-这样很不好,因为… -这样使我的WENUS出现问题
-Which is bad,because...? -lt throws my WENUS out of whack.
-对不起? -WENUS…
-Excuse me? -WENUS.
每周估计净值使用统计
Weekly Estimated Net Usage Statistics.
对
Gotcha!
不会再发生了 我不会做任何事伤害你的WENUS
Won't happen again. I wouldn't want to do anything to hurt your WENUS.
要我就在“工厂里的白痴”上押200,亚里克斯
I'll take "ldiots in the Workplace" for 200,Alex.
这不是她漂不漂亮的问题,这是…
It's not just that she's cute,okay? It's just that...
她真的很漂亮
...she's really,really cute.
都一样,你不能用公司的墨水填充自己的钢笔
It doesn't matter. You don't dip your pen in the company ink.
上帝,我知道我几乎不应该被雇用
God,I even know that and I'm pretty much unemployable.
罗斯，你的小动物又在玩遥控器
Ross,your little creature's got the remote again.
马修,把遥控器给罗斯
Marcel,give Rossy the remote.
马修!
Marcel!
马修,现在马上把遥控器给罗斯
Marcel,you give Rossy the remote right now!
把遥控器给罗斯
You give Rossy the remote
-这下好了 -放心.我会修好的
-Great. -Relax. I'll fix it.
（西班牙语）
乌克这个名字在西班牙文中叫“乌酷”
Oh,cool! Urkel in Spanish is Urkel.
他是怎么办到的?
How did he do this?
你还让圣诞灯开着是想让我们“快乐”一整年?
Is leaving Christmas lights up your plan to keep us merry all year long?
不,某人在新年期间就应该把它拿下 她显然是忘了
No,someone was supposed to take them down but obviously someone forgot.
某人应该写个字条“瑞秋,拿下圣诞灯”
Someone was supposed to write,"Rach,take down the lights"...
然后贴在冰…
...and put it on the refrigera
-在这儿多久了? -时间可不短了
-How long has that been there? -A really long time.
-你上哪儿去了? -瑞菲餐厅
-Where you been? -Riff's.
我想乌苏拉喜欢我 我只点咖啡
I think Ursula likes me. I ordered coffee.
她却端给我鲔鱼和四盘的薯片
She brought me a tuna melt and four plates of curly fries.
有门了
Score.
她好辣
She is so hot!
你展开“乔伊”行动之前,或许你可以找…
Before you do anything Joey-like,you might want to run it by....
-菲比? -当然
-Pheebs? -Yeah.
菲比,我约你姐出去你会介意吗?
Is it okay if I asked out your sister?
为什么?你为何要那样做?为什么?
Why? Why would you want to do that? Why?
因为如果我去约会时,她就会在我身边
So if we went out on a date,she'd be there.
好吧,不管怎样,我不是她
Well,I'm not my sister's,you know,whatever.
没错,我们确实曾待在同一颗卵子
And I mean,it's true,we were one egg once.
但我们各自发育
But you know,we've grown apart so....
我不知道…有何不可?
I don't know. Why not?
酷.谢啦
Cool. Thanks.
-你还好吧? -还好
-You okay? -Yeah,I'm fine.
你还要继续看拉乌妮・舍丽吗?
Do you wanna watch Laverney Shirley?
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉,我迟到了.卡萝在哪儿?
Hi. Sorry I'm late. Where's Carol?
学校有事,老师和家长间的事
Stuck at school. Some parent-teacher thing.
你可以走了,我留下来上课
You can go. I'll get the information.
不…我应该留下来 我们两个都该留下来上课
No,I think I should stay. We should both know what's going on.
很好,一定会很有意思的
Oh,good. This will be fun.
首先是第三阶段基本呼吸练习
We're gonna start with some basic third-stage breathing exercises.
各位妈妈请躺下
Moms,get on your back.
教练们支撑妈妈们的头
And coaches,you should be supporting Mommy's head.
-什么? -什么?
-What? -What?
-我该当妈妈吗? -好吧,我再一次拿精子说事儿
-I'm supposed to be the mommy? -I'll play my sperm card once more.
只因我是个女人 我就得错过教练训练？
I have to miss the coaching training because I'm a woman?
-了解,你说该怎么办? -掷铜板
-So,what do we do? -I'll flip you for it.
掷铜板?不…我选头…
Flip me for it? No,no. Heads!
躺下吧,妈
On your back,Mom!
各位妈妈们,请深呼吸
All right,mommies,take a nice deep,cleansing breath.
很好
Good.
很好,现在请想像你的阴道 像花一样绽放着
Now imagine your vagina is opening like a flower.
-迪先生,如何? -好多了
-Mr. D! How's it going,sir? -It's been better.
年度净值已经算出来了
The Annual Net Usage Statistics are in.
-然后呢? -奇惨无此
-And? -It's pretty ugly.
70年代之后没见过这么惨的ANUS
We haven't seen an ANUS this bad since the '70s.
-这代表什么? -每个部门都得裁员
-What does this mean? -We'll be laying off people.
我知道虽然我上星期迟到,我那天睡姿不良把头发睡塌
I know I was late last week. But I slept funny and
不是你,放松
Not you. Relax.
曾经必须开除某人吗?
Ever have to fire anyone?
没有,不过那不成问题. 这就是我的名字在门上的原因啊
No,but that's not a problem. That's why my name's on the door.
你知道我什么时候,能在门上有自己的名字吗?
Do you know when I'm getting my name on the door?
我不清楚.我会记下来的
I don't know. I put it in the thing.
不说这些.那将会是谁呢?
It's okay. So,who is it gonna be?
妮娜!
Nina!
妮娜
Nina.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
是的,我没事
Yes. Yes,I am.
听着,我今天叫你进来…是因为
Listen,the reason that I called you in here today was....
请别恨我
Please don't hate me.
怎么了?
What?
能约你共进晚餐吗?
Would you like to have dinner sometime?
菲比,你想要什么生日礼物?
So,what do you want for your birthday?
我想要我妈复活和我共享人生
What I want is for my mom to be alive and enjoy it with me.
好吧.这样吧.想不想要克拉布特里和伊夫琳（礼品公司）的产品?
Okay. Let me put it this way. Anything from Crabtree & Evelyn?
-我想要浴盐! -好的!
-Bath salts would be nice! -Okay! Good.
（海伦・亨特）
Helen Hunt
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
你很冷,我想尿尿,窗户上有个咖啡杯 还有比这更糟的吗?
You're cold,I have to pee and there's coffee. How bad could it be?
我想我们有答案了
I think we have an answer.
她怎么会在这儿?
Why is she here?
也许这就是老天爷叫我们回家吃饭的方法
This could be God's way of telling us to eat at home.
-她被瑞菲餐厅开除? -不,昨晚我们还在那儿吃饭,她不断端来剑鱼
-Think Riff's fired her? -No,we were there last night.
你不是要去…?
Are you gonna go to the...?
-不,点完之后再去 -是她吧?看起来像她
-I'll wait till we order. It's her. -lt looks like her.
-抱歉? -是
-Excuse me? -Yeah.
是我们
Hi,it's us!
好呀,是我
Right. And it's me!
-你也在这儿? -和你们一样
-So you're here too? -As much as you are.
该你了
Your turn.
-我们知道我们要什么 -很好
-We know what we want. -That's good.
我们要两杯拿铁还有小饼干
-Two caffe lattes. -And some biscotti.
不错的选择
Good choice.
-绝对是她 -绝对是她
-It's definitely her. -Yeah.
我真不敢相信,你还没告诉她她失业了?
I can't believe you haven't told that girl she doesn't have a job.
你还没把圣诞灯拿下来
You haven't taken down the Christmas lights.
恭喜!你发现了世上最薄弱的论点
Congratulations! You've found the world's thinnest argument.
我只是在寻找适当的时机
I'm finding the right moment.
应该不会太难找到 因为你们已开始约会
That shouldn't be so hard now that you're dating.
亲爱的,你被开除了 我上班前何不来个“速战速决”
"Honey,you're fired. But how about a quickie before I go to work?"
进门后就不用再敲门了
Once you're inside,you don't have to knock anymore.
我来开
I'll get it.
-哈克先生 -你们又来了
-Hi,Mr. Heckles. -You're doing it again.
我们什么都没做. 我们只是坐在这儿静静地聊天
We're not doing anything. We're sitting and talking quietly.
我可以透过天花板听见
I can hear you through the ceiling.
我的猫睡不着
My cats can't sleep.
-你根本没养猫 -我原本有机会养
-You don't even have cats. -I could have cats.
-再见了,哈克先生 -我们会很小声的
-Goodbye,Mr. Heckles. -We'll try to keep it down.
菲比,帮个忙,能试穿看看吗? 我想知道合不合身?
Phoebe,do me a favor. Try this on. I want to make sure it fits.
我的第一件生日礼物,这衣服真…
My first birthday present! This is really
不,是送乌苏拉的,我只是想知道尺寸
No,no,it's for Ursula. I just figured size-wise....
好呀,合身
Sure. Yeah. Okay,it fits.
-你今晚又和她约会? -对,去看白雪溜冰团（冰上舞蹈表演团体）
-Are you seeing her again? -Yep,lce Capades.
这回你是来真的 没想到你会为任何花式玩意儿付钱
This is serious. I've never known you to pay for any kind of "capade."
我也不知道,我喜欢她
I don't know. I like her.
她与众不同,她有…
She's different. There's something about her
你喜欢?我们懂 你喜欢她,太好了
That you like. We get it. You like her. Great!
菲比,我问过你而你也同意了
Phoebe,I asked you. You said it was okay.
也许现在不同意了
Maybe now it's not okay.
也许我对于你的不同意也不同意了
Okay. Maybe now I'm not okay with it not being okay.
好吧!
Okay!
快织，好女人，快织
IKnit,good woman,knit!
克莱斯勒大楼就在那儿
And that's the Chrysler Building right there.
-妮娜! -道格拉斯先生.领带不错
-Nina! -Mr. Douglas. Cool tie.
她还在这里?
She's still here.
没错,她还在.我没有给你这个备忘录吗?
Yes. Yes,she is. Didn't I memo you on this?
我开除她后,接到她心理医生的电话
After I let her go,I got a call from her psychiatrist,Dr. Flennan
佛…佛林大夫
Dr. Flennan Dr. Flynn.
他说她一时无法适应
And he informed me that she took the news rather badly.
老实说他提到“狂暴”这两个字
In fact,he mentioned the word "frenzy."
-她?开什么玩笑?她…  -不,妮娜?她…
-You're kidding! She seems so -No. Nina? She's
如果你现在问她
If you asked her now...
她根本记不得被开除这件事
...she'd have no recollection of being fired at all.
-难以置信 -你不得不信
-That's unbelievable. -And yet believable.
因此我决定不再开除她直到她对其他人不构成威胁为止
So I decided not to fire her again until she'll be no threat to anyone.
人的心中在想什么 别人永远无法完全了解
I guess you never know what's going on inside a person's head.
我想这就是为什么被成为“心理学”了，先生
Well,I guess that's why they call it psychology,sir.
爸妈永远忘不了这声音
The sound Mom and Dad will never forget.
这个,毕竟是生产的奇迹
For this,after all,is the miracle of birth.
请开灯,这一集是生宝宝
Lights,please. And that's having a baby.
下周是我们的最后一堂课
Next week is our final class.
苏珊,准备接球
Susan,go deep.
-这太离谱了… -怎么了?亲爱的
-It's just impossible. -What is,honey?
那个女人干了什么
What that woman did.
我不会这么做的.他得留在我体内
I am not doing that. It'll just have to stay in.
一切和原来一样,他得留在我体内
Everything will be the same. It'll just stay in.
-卡萝,亲爱的,不会有事的 -你怎么知道?
-Carol,honey,it'll be all right. -What do you know?
没人问你,我能将这肉块穿你的鼻孔吗?
No one's asking you,"Mind if we push this pot roast through your nostril?"
卡萝,亲爱的,深呼吸
Carol,sweetie. Cleansing breath.
我知道你很惶恐,往远处想
I know it's frightening. But big picture:
生产过程只是一天
The birth part is just one day.
结束后我们这辈子都是他的父母了
When it's over,we'll all be parents for the rest of our lives.
怀胎生子为的不就是这些吗?罗斯?
I mean,that's what this is all about,right? Ross?
罗斯?
Ross?
我要当爸爸了
I'm gonna be a father.
-你才刚知道? -我一直都知道我有个孩子
-This is news to you? -I knew I was having a baby.
只是不知道孩子有我
I just never realized the baby was having me.
-你会是个好爸爸的 -你怎会知道?
-You'll be great. -How can you say that?
我连阻止马修吃浴室垫都办不到
I can't even get Marcel to stop eating the bathmat.
-我如何抚养孩子? -罗斯,科学家说
-How will I raise a kid? -Some scientists are now saying...
孩子和猴子是不一样的
...that monkeys and babies are actually different.
我们可以验证一下
You might want to look into it.
-你去哪里? -外面
-Where you going? -Out.
和谁?
With...?
是的
Yes.
能问你一个问题吗?
Can I just ask you one question?
你们有没有…,你明白的,就像,你知道的嘛?
Have you two,you know,like,you know?
你知道的,对吧?
You know,yet?
不关你的事,没有,行了吗?
Not that it's any of your business,but no,we haven't.
你是指性吧?
You meant sex,right?
-有空吗? -当然,什么事?
-Do you have a sec? -Sure. What's up?
最近几天,大家都避开我 而且以奇怪的眼神看我
The past few days,people have been avoiding me and giving me weird looks.
或许他们在嫉妒我们
Well,maybe that's because they're jealous of us.
或许吧,这无法解释他们为何拿走我的剪刀
Maybe. But that doesn't explain why they keep taking my scissors.
或许是因为你被升职的缘故
Maybe that's because you're getting a big raise!
-我升职了? -当然.为什么不呢?
-I am? -Sure. Why not?
天啊,你真是太了不起了
Oh,my God! You're amazing!
你不知道
You don't know.
海伦,能快处理布克宾得小姐升职的手续吗?
Helen,do the paperwork on Miss Bookbinder's raise.
你仍要我拿她的心理分析结果到人事部?
You still want me to send her psychological profile to Personnel?
海伦喝醉了
Helen drinks.
你愿意嫁给我吗?
Will you marry me?
升职后的事情,我就未经修剪了
So after the proposal,I kind of unraveled.
是啊.因为你控制全盘直到那个时候
Right. Because you were really in control up until then.
-最后我把一切都告诉她了 -她的反应如何?
-I told her everything. -How'd she take it?
还不错,除了拿钉书机钉我之外
Pretty well. Except for the stapler thing.
提示一下.以后遇见类似的状况
A tip. If you're ever in a similar situation...
切记别把手放在桌上
... never,ever leave your hand on the desk.
我知道该怎么调这个了
Okay,I think I get how to do this.
我们能把这关掉吗? 把他们弄走,因为我没法看了啊
Can we turn it off? Make them go away because I can't watch.
好了,现在没有了
Okay,they're gone.
你还好吧?
Are you all right?
还不是乌苏拉惹的祸
It's just this whole stupid Ursula thing.
菲比,我能问… 他和她约会真有那么糟吗?
Pheebs,can I ask? So he's going out with her. Is it really so terrible?
是的
Yeah.
我不是说她很坏
I'm not saying she's evil or anything.
她总是弄坏我的东西
She's just always breaking my stuff.
我8岁时,她把我的朱迪杰特森热水壶丢到公共汽车下
When I was 8,she threw my Judy Jetson Thermos under the bus.
我12岁的时候,她弄断了我的锁骨
And then when I was 1 2,she broke my collarbone.
她不是有意的,不过也算
She didn't mean to do it but I think it still counts.
然后,有个蓝迪布朗,就像
And then there's Randy Brown,who was like
你们有没有过男友身兼好友的情况?
Have you ever had a boyfriend who was your best friend?
我当时的状况就是如此
That's what he was for me.
她把他抢走又伤了他的心
And she kind of stole him away and then broke his heart.
他从此不和我说话
Then he wouldn't talk to me anymore.
因为他说他不愿再见像她的人
He didn't want to be around anything that looked like either one of us.
我知道乔伊不是我男朋友或者热水壶
I know Joey's not my boyfriend or my thermos...
或其他的什么,但是
...or anything,but
-你不会失去他的 -你得找乔伊谈谈
-You won't lose him. -You gotta talk to Joey.
-如果他知道你的感受 -但他爱上她了
-lf he knew how you felt -But he's falling in love with her.
拜托,他们才约会一个星期
They've been going out a week.
根本还没上床，事情还没那么糟
They haven't even slept together yet. That's not serious.
好吧.好吧
Okay. Okay.
需要帮忙吗?
May we help you?
瑞秋,你在干什么?外面好冷,进来好吗?
What are you doing? It's freezing! Come inside.
不…你要我把灯取下
No,you wanted me to take them down...
我正在做,行吗?
...so I'm taking them down,okay?
天啊,瑞秋!
Rachel!
我没事…
I'm okay. I'm okay.
哈克先生…
Mr. Heckles?
哈克先生…能帮一下忙吗?
Mr. Heckles,could you help me,please?
我指的就是这种事儿
This is just the kind of thing I was talking about.
我朋友取下圣诞灯时
My friend was taking down Christmas lights...
从阳台跌下来,可能伤了脚踝
...and may have broken her ankle.
你们的圣诞灯还亮着?
My God,you still have your Christmas lights up?
-填好资料后拿给我 给
-Fill this out and bring it back. -Here you go.
姓名?地址
All right. Name,address.
-你有进行任何药物治疗吗? -没有
-Are you currently on any medication? -No.
哦,等等!有.Blistex（一种药用润唇膏）
Oh,wait! Yes. Blistex.
-填没有，紧急联络电话? -你
-No. In case of emergency,call...? -You.
-真的? -对
-Really? -Yeah.
你真好
Oh,that is so sweet!
我爱你.保险?
Gosh,love you. Okay,insurance?
哦,打勾,我当然需要保险
Oh,yeah,check it. Definitely gonna want some of that!
-你没有保险? -要多少钱?
-You don't have insurance? -How much will this cost?
单是X光就可能得要两百元
X-rays alone could be $200!
-我们该怎么办? -没有太多办法可想
-What are we gonna do? -There's not much we can do.
除非我用你的
Unless I use yours.
-不,不,不 -等等
-No,no,no. -Now wait a second.
我的紧急联络人是谁?
Who did I just put as my emergency person?
这是保险欺诈
That's insurance fraud.
好吧.算了.我回家
All right then,forget it. Might as well just go home.
-好吧,回来,我真讨厌这样做 -谢谢?我爱你
-Okay,come here. I hate this. -Thank you. I love you.
我需要新表格
Hi. I'm gonna need a new set of these forms.
-为什么? -我真是个笨蛋
-Why? -I am really an idiot.
我替我朋友填资料时
I was filling out her form...
填的不是她的资料而是我的
...and instead of putting her information I put mine.
你真是个笨蛋
You are an idiot.
没错?这就是我.我就是那么笨
Yep,that's me. I am that stupid.
我梦见我和我儿子在玩橄榄球
I had a dream. I was playing football with my kid.
-真温馨 -不?他是球
-That's nice. -No,no. With him.
我在球场上,他们叫我以儿子做裆下开球
I'm on this field,and they hike me the baby.
我得做点什么,坦帕湾队的防守球员逐渐逼近
I've gotta do something. The Tampa Bay defense is coming right at me!
-坦帕湾队烂得可怕 -没错
-Tampa Bay's got a terrible team. -Right,but...
但只有我和我儿子.我想我们死定了
...it is just me and the baby,so I'm thinking they can take us.
所以我只好传球
And so I just heave it downfield!
-什么?你疯啦?他是你儿子 -他能控制住球吗?
-What are you,crazy? That's a baby! -He should take the sack?
总之,突然我又到了前场
Anyway,suddenly I'm downfield.
我发现该接球的人是我
And I realize I'm the one who's supposed to catch him.
但我绝对来不及
I know I'm not gonna get there in time.
于是我跑啊跑,然后就惊醒了
So I am running and running. That is when I woke up.
看?我还没准备好当爸爸
See? I am so not ready to be a father.
你没问题的
You're gonna be fine.
你是全北美最细心,最有责任感的男人
You're one of the most caring,responsible men in North America.
你将来一定是个好爸爸的
You're gonna make a great dad.
没错 你和你儿子,只是需要更好的防守
Yeah,you and the baby just need better blocking.
你们去过彩虹厅吗?真有那么贵?
Have you ever been to the Rainbow Room? Is it expensive?
当然,只有你要了东西才会贵
Well,only if you order stuff.
我今晚要带乌苏拉去,今天是她生日
I'm taking Ursula tonight. It's her birthday.
-菲比的生日该怎么办? -什么时候?
-What about Phoebe's birthday? -When's that?
-今晚 -怎么会有这么巧的事情发生呢?
-Tonight. -What are the odds of that happening?
慢慢想吧
You take your time.
原来是这样啊!
There it is!
-你打算怎么办? -我能怎么办?
-What'll you do? -What can I do?
我不想让乌苏拉不开心
I don't wanna screw it up with Ursula.
你的朋友菲比呢?
And your friend?
如果她是我朋友希望她能谅解. 你们能谅解吗?
If she's my friend,she'll understand. Wouldn't you?
我生日时如果你敢这样做
If you tried that on my birthday...
我就和你没完没了
...you'd be staring at the end of a hissy fit.
加上少量蕃红花,就能使情况完全改观
Saffron makes all the difference.
（乔治・克鲁尼 诺亚・怀尔）
George Clooney&Noah Wyle
-莫妮卡? -是…
-Okay. Monica? -Yes.
-是…她 -她是我朋友瑞秋
-Yes,she is. -Hi,this is my friend Rachel.
-瑞秋?我是米契尔大夫 -我是罗森大夫
-Hi,I'm Dr. Mitchell. -And I'm Dr. Rosen.
我在这没问题
I'm okay here.
好吧,就这样.你可以休息一下
Actually,that's all right. You can take your break.
不了,这就是我为什么做了医生. 脚踝之类是我的专长
No,this is why I became a doctor. Ankles and stuff like that.
-你当医生是否太帅了一点? -什么?
-Aren't you too cute to be a doctor? -Excuse me?
天哪,年轻,我是指年轻 你当医生稍显年轻了点,说得好,瑞秋
God,young,young. I meant young. Young to be a doctor. Good,Rach.
-谢谢 -好的
-Thank you. -Right.
他说这只是扭伤
He said it was just a sprain.
-你忘了说我们做的蠢事 -才不蠢呢
-You left out the stupid part. -It's not stupid.
这两位帅哥大夫约我们明晚出去,我答应了
The cute doctors asked us out for tomorrow,and I said yes.
你根本就是疯了,他们在医院工作
I think it's insane. They work for the hospital.
我们这样不是回到犯罪现场吗?
It's like returning to the scene of the crime.
-还是取消约会吧 -什么?他们可是大帅哥
-I say we blow off the dates. -What? They are cute.
而且还是医生.帅哥医生?很帅的医生
They are doctors. Cute doctors. Doctors who are cute.
目前为止我们了解到什么?
All right,what have we learned so far?
天啊
Oh,God. Okay.
惊喜
Surprise!
你们在干什么?把我吓死了!
What are you doing? You scared the crap out of me!
-那是蛋糕吗? -对?柠檬口味
-Was that the cake? -Yeah. I got a lemon schmoosh.
赶快，她随时会到
Come on. She'll be here any minute.
希望蛋糕没事
Hope it's okay.
“生日快乐?菲…”
"Happy Birthday Peehee."
或许我们可以用玫瑰当“比”
Maybe we can make a "B" out of a rose.
对?用我们的特殊蛋糕工具
We'll just use our special cake tools.
-什么事? -我们只是
-What's going on? -We just
惊喜!
Surprise!
你们真是太好了,一点都不吓人
This is so great! Oh,my God! This was not at all scary.
看哪!“生日快乐,菲”
Look! "Happy Birthday Peehee."
好奇怪的昵称啊.我好喜欢,哦上帝!
What a strange new nickname. I like it! Oh,my God!
嗨，各位。嗨，贝蒂!贝蒂!
Hi,everybody. Hi,Betty! Betty,hi!
你找到贝蒂了?太好了
You found Betty! Oh,my gosh! This is so great.
我爱的大家都在一起,乔伊在哪儿?
Everybody I love is in the same room. Where's Joey?
你看见贝蒂没?
Did you see Betty?
我不介意去做蕃茄干的生意
I wouldn't mind having a piece of this sun-dried tomato business.
五年前如果有人说我的蕃茄像李子
Five years ago,if somebody had said,"A tomato that's like a prune"...
我就叫他滚出我的办公室
... I'd have said,"Get out!"
爸爸 我出生前你会紧张吗?
Dad,before I was born,did you freak out?
我不紧张,我是说如果有人对我说…
I'm not freaking out! I'm saying,if someone had come to me
爸 我在谈小孩的事
Dad,I'm talking about the whole baby thing.
你是否曾因为
Did you ever get this sort of...
将成为父亲而紧张?
... panicky,"Oh,my God,I'm gonna be a father" thing?
不会.我们只是要回收种子
No. We just had kids back then.
我们根本就不想这些. 我在想除了晒干还能怎么办?
We didn't think about it. What else could the sun dry,I wonder?
老爸,不要这样,我们在说孩子
Dad,come on. IKids.
都是你妈在处理,我忙着事业
Look,your mother really did the work. I was busy with the business.
经常不在家,你找我来是为了这个?
I wasn't around that much. Is that what this is about?
不是?我只是有点迷惑
No,I was just wondering.
因为我们有时间弥补 我们可以一起做某些事
We can make up for that. We can do stuff together.
你一直想去威廉斯堡,我们一起去吧?
You always wanted to go to Colonial Williamsburg. Let's do that.
谢了,爸.我只是
Thanks,Dad,really. You know,I just....
我只是想知道
I just needed to know...
你何时感觉自己像个父亲
...when did you start to feel like a father?
应该是你出生那一天
Well,I guess it must've been the day after you were born.
我们在病房,你妈在睡觉
We were in the hospital room,your mom was asleep...
他们把你交给我
...and they brought you in and gave you to me.
你当时又丑又红又小
You were this ugly little red thing.
你突然用拳头紧抓住我的手指
All of a sudden you grabbed my finger with your fist...
紧紧捏住我的手指
...and you squeezed it so tight.
那时候我才感觉到
And that's when I knew.
你不想去威廉斯堡?
So you don't wanna go to Williamsburg?
我们可以去
We can go to Williamsburg.
吃鱼吧
Eat your fish.
-瑞秋 帅哥医生来了! -来了
-Rachel,the cute doctors are here! -Okay,coming.
-请进 -你好,麦可.杰佛瑞
-Hi,come on in. -Hi,Jeffrey.
我们带了一瓶酒
We brought wine.
这是来自欧内斯特和托娃博格宁的酒窖（演员和酒类收藏家）
Look. It's from the cellars of Ernest and Tova Borgnine.
-我们怎么能够拒绝呢? -太好了!
-How could we resist? -That's great!
-莫妮卡,脚踝如何? -它啊
-Monica,how's the ankle? -It's....
你何不告诉他们,这可是你的脚踝
Why don't you tell them? After all,it is your ankle.
感觉好多了,谢谢
It's feeling a lot better. Thank you.
你们请坐 我去拿杯子
Why don't you guys sit down,and we'll get you some glasses?
请坐
Okay. Stat!
我们何不表明我们的身份 绝对不会有事的
Why don't we just tell them who we really are? It'll be fine.
-我们会惹上大麻烦 -莫妮卡,别那么不争气
-We'll get in trouble. -Would you stop being such a wuss?
不争气?抱歉,我生在真实的世界之中
A wuss? Excuse me for living in the real world.
所以呢?她们似乎很正常
-So? -So they still seem normal.
但你得承认
Because they are.
每次我们和女病患约会都…
When we go out with women from the hospital
别紧张,看看四周.没有异教徒的神坛
Relax. Take a look around. There are no pagan altars.
角落没有成堆的骨头,她们没事的,这个…
No piles of bones in the corners. They're fine. Go like this:
我们绝不能这么做,有时你真的很幼稚
We're not going to do it. Sometimes you can be such a baby!
-我才不幼稚 -严格来说,每次都是
-I am not a baby. -Be serious. Every time
-你像个公主… -你知道吗?
-You act like a princess. -You know what?
你愈来愈像你妈了
Every day you are becoming more and more like your mother. Excuse me.
来了
Here we go.
这房子好漂亮,住在这儿多久了?
Great place. How long have you lived here?
谢谢,我住在这儿六年了
I've been here about six years.
瑞秋几个月前才搬来
And Rachel moved in a few months ago.
对,我本来应该结婚的 但我在圣坛前撇开了新郎
See,I was supposed to get married,but I left the guy at the altar.
-真的? -是的
-Really? -Yeah.
对,我知道我很自私 但我就是这种人
Yeah,I know it's pretty selfish,but hey,that's me!
-试试这个鹰嘴豆沙 -莫妮卡,你从事什么工作?
-Try the hummus. -Monica,what do you do?
我是上城区一家餐厅的总厨师
I am a chef at a restaurant uptown.
-真有你的 -没错
-Good for you. -Yeah,it is.
因为我喜欢指使别人
Mostly because I get to boss people around,which I just love to do.
-这个鹰嘴豆沙不错. -上帝保佑鹰嘴豆
-This hummus is great. -God bless the chickpea.
我真是被宠坏了
Oh,God! I am so spoiled!
就这样了
That's it.
我偷东西
I shoplift.
你绝对想不到唇膏在我的口袋中
You had no idea that lipstick was in your pocket.
我告诉过你们我比原来可爱多了吗?
Did I tell you that I think I'm so much cuter than I am?
对了,我有提过,我在高中是只肥牛吗?
And have I mentioned that back in high school I was a cow?
我常尿床
I used to wet my bed.
我以胸部吸引别人的注意
I use my breasts to get people's attention.
我们都一样
We both do that!
莫妮卡与瑞秋的公寓
Monica and Rachel's apartment.
等等,瑞秋,是你爸
Just one second. Rachel,it's your dad.
爸?不,是我
Hi,Dad. No,no,it's me.
听我说,老爸,我现在没空
Listen,Dad,I can't talk right now.
但有些
But there's something....
有些话我一直想告诉你
There's something I've been meaning to tell you.
-失陪一下。-记得我大一时吗?
-Excuse me. -Remember back in freshman year?
我和比利在你床上做爱
Well,Billy Dreskin and I had sex on your bed.
爸
Daddy.
为什么?我干嘛和比利上床?
Why? Why would I sleep with Billy Dreskin?
他爸想害你倒闭!你死定了!
His father tried to put you out of business! You are dead!
嗨,瑞秋?这是你的保险套吗?
Hey,Rachel? Are these your condoms?
哦,不,那是莫妮卡.她又喝醉了
Oh,no,that was just Monica. She's drunk again.
我不记得“scrunchy”是一个词
I don't think "scrunchy" is a word.
为什么不是,“嘎吱嘎吱”都是一个词呢?
Why not,if "crunchy" is a word?
那这么说“fligament”也是词了啊
Then I'm using that same argument for "fligament."
-罗斯,他又在玩遥控器了 -好的
-Ross,he's got the remote again. -Good.
或许他能将功能变回来
Maybe he can switch it back.
或许不会
Maybe not.
爸爸 有电话进来了
Okay,Daddy? That's the other line.
没有,没有,也没有在我的卧室里做过
Okay,no,not even in my bedroom.
好的好的，再见
Okay. Okay. Bye-bye.
你好?
Hello?
等等,我看看她在不在
Hold on a second. Let me check and see if she's here.
医院那个女人打来的,她说表格有问题
It's the woman from the hospital. There's a problem.
-我们该怎么办? -你去问他们想干什么
-What do we do? -Just find out what they want.
不,你问
Okay. No,you do it.
我是莫妮卡,是的?
Hello. This is Monica. Yeah?
好,我们马上去,谢谢
Oh,okay. Yes,we'll be right down. Thank you.
什么事?我们忘了签名
We forgot to sign one of the admissions forms.
你说得对,不值得这么做.我们改回来
You were right. This was just not worth it. Let me just change.
-“Garge”? -航海时代
-"Garge"? -Nautical term.
-作弊男 -好吧
-Cheating man. -Okay.
-她还没有打电话？ -没有
-She still didn't call? -No.
有心事?
Trouble?
你妹放我鸽子
Your sister stood me up.
被人放鸽子的滋味不好受吧
Don't you hate it when people aren't there for you?
-这是什么? -“屁股.”
-What is that? -"Tushy."
-你有打电话给她吗? -我连打了两天
-Did you try calling her? -For two days.
打到餐厅时他们说她太忙
At the restaurant they said she was busy.
我不敢相信她想甩掉我
I can't believe she's blowing me off!
-我们点了两份厨师沙拉 -它们怎么了?
-We had the two chef salads. -And how were they?
不,我们还没有吃.我们只是希望吃那个
No,we haven't had them yet. We're still hoping to have them.
好吧
Okay.
-有空吗? -有,我只是在工作
-You got a minute? -Yeah,I'm just working.
那…
So.
-我为你买了生日礼物 -呜,你记得
-I got you a birthday present. -Wow,you remembered.
-是个朱迪杰特森热水壶 -对,像你…
-It's a Judy Jetson thermos. -Like the kind you
对,我也有东西送你
Right. Oh,I got something for you too.
-你怎知道我会来? -我们是双胞胎嘛
-How'd you know I was coming? -Yeah,twin thing.
我不敢相信你会这么做
I can't believe you did this.
你和乔伊之间呢?
So,what's the deal with you and Joey?
他人很好,但我们结束了
Oh,right. He is so great. But that's over.
-他知道吗? -谁?
-Does he know? -Who?
乔伊.他对你着迷不已
Joey. You know,he's really nutsy about you.
-是吗?为什么? -你可把我问倒了
-He is? Why? -You got me.
没错.抱歉,这道菜不是有杂菜沙拉吗?
Right. Excuse me,doesn't this come with a side salad?
你会打电话给他吗?
So are you gonna call him?
-你认为他喜欢我? -不,是乔伊
-You think he likes me? -No. Joey.
不,他很聪明,他会了解的
Oh! No,he is so smart. He'll figure it out.
想吃鸡肉?
Do you want some chicken?
不.有脸的食物不吃,记得吗?
No. No food with a face.
-你还是没变 -你也一样
-You have not changed. -Yeah,you too.
谢谢.抱歉?我的杂菜沙拉在哪?
Thanks. Excuse me? My side salad?
这里的服务很差.现在我明白为什么了
Service here is horrible. Now I know what people mean.
记得我们吗?
Hi! Remember us?
你刚打电话要我们过来在表格上签名?
You called about needing a signature on the form?
但我们需要一张全新的表格
Well,it turns out we need a new one.
我又写错名字了
Because,you see,I put the wrong name again.
-因为… -你就是那么笨
-Because -You're that stupid!
对,我就是那么笨
I am. I'm that stupid.
我要用支票付帐
And I'm gonna pay for this with a check.
你有保险可以付的
Your insurance will cover that.
我知道,只是我也没那么聪明
I know. I'm just not that bright either.
莫妮卡,对不起,我不是真的认为你像你妈妈
Mon,I'm sorry. I don't think you're like your mother.
没关系.我也不认为你逃婚很自私
That's all right. And I don't think you were selfish.
哦,对不起我说你以前是肥牛
Oh,and I'm sorry I said you were a cow.
没关系,我就是肥牛
That's okay,I was a cow.
我知道,我只是为我说了这话抱歉
I know. I'm just sorry I said it.
最糟糕的情况是,你从未感觉像个爸爸
Worst case scenario: Say you never feel like a father.
你儿子从未感觉你像个爸爸
Say your son never feels connected to you as one.
他所有的关系全受这个的影响
Say all of his relationships are affected by this.
-你这话有没有重点? -应该有的
-Do you have a point? -You know,you'd think I would.
这只猴子到底怎么了?
What's up with the simian?
-只是毛球 -好吧
-It's just a fur ball. -All right.
-该谁了? -你.我的kidney（肾脏）得了43分
-Whose turn? -Yours. I got 43 points for "kidney."
不,你没得分.你拼的是“idney”
No,you got zero points for "idney."
不,我有k,我的k在哪儿?
I had a "K." Where's my "K"?
快帮我,我的猴子把k吞了
You've got to help me! My monkey swallowed a "K"!
-把你的动物带走! -不,你不懂.动物医院离这儿很远
-Get that animal out! -The animal hospital is across town.
-怎么回事? -马修吞了一个字母
-What's going on? -Marcel swallowed a Scrabble tile.
抱歉,这是为人看病的医院
Excuse me. This hospital is for people!
小姐,他是人,他有名字
He is people! He has a name,okay?
他也爱看“幸运轮”,没人看见时它就摸自己
He watches Jeopardy!,he touches himself when nobody's watching.
拜托,发挥你的爱心
Please,have a heart.
-我替它看看 -谢谢
-I'll take a look at him. -Thanks.
-麦克! -瑞秋
-Michael! -Rachel.
-什么? -莫尼卡
-What? -Monica.
乌苏拉?你怎么会在这儿? 我一直打电话找你
Urs,what are you doing here? I've been trying to call you.
听我说
Listen....
不,别叫我听.我知道你的意思 我也叫人听我说过
Don't say "listen." I know that "listen." I've said that.
-抱歉 -我不懂,你怎么了?
-I'm sorry. -I don't get it. What happened?
你在桥下说过的话呢?
What about what you said under the bridge?
你得忘记我在桥下说过的话
Yeah. You should just forget about what I said under the bridge.
我那一夜喝醉了,胡言乱语
I was talking crazy that night. I was so drunk.
-你不喝酒 -没错,我不喝酒
-You don't drink. -That's right,I don't.
-但我爱你爱得如痴如醉 -乌苏拉
-But I was drunk on you. -Oh,Urs
我们是没有结果的
But it's not gonna work.
为什么?因为我是菲比的朋友?
Why? Is it because I'm friends with Phoebe?
如果是,你愿意不和她来往吗?
Would you stop hanging out with her?
不行,我办不到
No,I couldn't do that.
没错,就是因为她
Then yeah,it's because of Phoebe.
所以,不是她就是我
So,you know,it's either her or me.
那么我只能说抱歉了
Then I'm sorry.
忘了你是很难的一件事
You know,you're gonna be really hard to get over.
我知道
I know.
我不知是否因为分手
I don't know whether it's just because we're breaking up or what.
-你从未这么漂亮过 -真的?
-But you've never looked so beautiful. -Really?
-菲比? -什么?
-Pheebs? -Yeah.
他看起来好小
He looks so tiny.
-我刚听说了 -他没事吧?
-We just heard. -ls he okay?
对?医生已取出k了
The doctor got the "K" out.
他还发现m和o
He also found an "M" and an "O."
他一定想拼monkey（猴子）
We think he was trying to spell out "monkey."
医生说他已无大碍,他睡着了
The doctor says he'll be fine. He's just sleeping now.
-你有当爸爸的感觉没? -没有,干嘛问?
-So,you feel like a dad yet? -No. Why?
拜托,你办到了.你做了必须做的
Come on,you came through. You did what you had to do.
-有爸爸的味道了 -看?他醒了
-That's very "dad." -Look. He's waking up.
老兄?感觉如何?
Hey,fella. How you doing?
（西班牙语）-给你这个 -谁点左将军鸡了？
Here it is.Who ordered General Tso's chicken?
也许是左将军本人点的
It could've been General Tso!
看呐，丑陋裸男在转呼啦圈
Look, look, Ugly Naked Guy is doing the hula!
-嗨，乔伊 -嗨，各位
Hi, Joey!Hey, everybody!
看呐罗斯，马修又在玩遥控器了
Look, Ross, Marcel's got the remote
那是因为它不喜欢这个节目
The thing is, he doesn`t like the program